Roxane Connick Carlisle collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: Photographs, Due to the small space in which to write on the slide mats, some of the information is unclear or difficult to understand. Carlisle's spelling of proper names of locations or ethnic groups reflect contemporary spelling. In these cases, the first instance is revised to reflec
  - Subseries 5: Ethnomusicology I - Northern singers and instrumentalists; Omdurman-Kordofan- Shilluk singers, drummers ritual for Nyikang at Akruwa; Upper Nile Province - Shilluk
    - Shilluk tribesmen; Kodoc Upper Nile Province; recording session, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0301 (Box 7)
    - Reth Kur Fafiti Yor at Kodoc, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0302 (Box 7)
    - Edward Umum of Lelo in Palaver Court at Kodoc, Upper Nile Province; recording session, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0303 (Box 7)
    - Reth Kur Papiti; Kodoc, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0304 (Box 7)
    - Reth Kur Papiti in traditional Shilluk dress; Kodoc, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0305 (Box 7)
    - Reth of Shilluk with girl singers in Kodoc before ritual dance, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0306 (Box 7)
    - Reth of Shilluk [?], 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0307 (Box 7)
    - Shilluk village men; Malakal, May 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0308 (Box 7)
    - Shilluk drum maker's village near Malakal; Upper Nile Province, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0309 (Box 7)
    - Shilluk drum maker near Malakal with his son, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0310 (Box 7)
    - Shilluk drum maker and my interpreter in village near Malakal; Upper Nile Province, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0311 (Box 7)
    - Shilluk drum maker's village near Malakal, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0312 (Box 7)
    - N. Shilluk drum and makers, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0313 (Box 7)
    - Shilluk drum maker's village near Malkal, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0314 (Box 7)
    - N. Shilluk carrying drum for American Museum of Natural History to my car, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0315 (Box 7)
    - Drum from Shilluk maker being loaded onto my car near Malakal; Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0316 (Box 7)
    - Nyikang's drums at Akurwa, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0317 (Box 7)
    - Shilluk thom musician; William Owoti; Malakal, Upper Nile Province, May 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0318 (Box 7)
    - Shilluk Thom; Tonga near Malakal, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0319 (Box 7)
    - Shilluk Thom; Tonga near Malakal, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0320 (Box 7)
    - Shilluk Thom; Tonga near Malakal, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0321 (Box 7)
  - Subseries 6: Ethnomusicology I - Northern singers and instrumentalists; Omdurman-Kordofan- Shilluk singers, drummers ritual for Nyikang at Akruwa; Upper Nile Province - Shilluk
    - Nuer taking me to their camp near Akobo, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0322 (Box 7)
    - My Nuer residence near Akobo, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0323 (Box 7)
    - Nuer chief; Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0324 (Box 7)
    - Female relative of Nuer chief near Akobo; Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0325 (Box 7)
    - Nuer settlement near Akobo; Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0326 (Box 7)
    - Nuer drummers; Akobo, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0327 (Box 7)
    - Nuer drummers; Akobo, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0328 (Box 7)
    - Anuak singers; Apogko, Dengushalla and Owoir, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0329 (Box 7)
    - Anuak singers, Akobo; Owoir, Dengushalla and Apogko, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0330 (Box 7)
    - Anuak dancers; Akobo, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0331 (Box 7)
    - Anuak dancers; Akobo, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0332 (Box 7)
    - Anuak dancers; Akobo, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0333 (Box 7)
    - Anuak before dance; Akobo, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0334 (Box 7)
    - Anuak drummers; Akobo, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0335 (Box 7)
    - Anuak singer; Deng Ushalla at Akobo, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0336 (Box 7)
    - Anuak singers; Akobo, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0337 (Box 7)
    - Anuak singers; Akobo, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0338 (Box 7)
    - Military convoy into Dinka area, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0339 (Box 7)
    - Gov. Osmar Nasr Osman, Upper Nile Province, in Dinka area, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0340 (Box 7)
    - Dinka and Nuer area near Fariang Riangnam, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0341 (Box 7)
    - People are dressed when they meet the governor; Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0342 (Box 7)
    - Dinkas dancing for the governor, Upper Nile Province, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0343 (Box 7)
    - Governor leaving Dinka assemblies, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0344 (Box 7)
    - Dinka at Fariang; Upper Nile Province, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0345 (Box 7)
    - Dinka at Fariang Upper Nile Province, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0346 (Box 7)
    - Dinka girls at Riangnam dressed for governor's review, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0347 (Box 7)
    - Dinka girls dressed for Governor's review; Riangnam, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0348 (Box 7)
    - Dinka girl dancers, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0349 (Box 7)
    - Dinka girl dancers, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0350 (Box 7)
    - Dinka and drum, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0351 (Box 7)
    - Dinka drummers at governor's reception, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0352 (Box 7)
    - W. Dinka drummers; South of Lake Abyad; Upper Nile Province, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0353 (Box 7)
    - W. Dinka drummers South of Lake Abyad; Upper Nile Province, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0354 (Box 7)
    - W. Dinka at drumming session near Lake Abyad, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0355 (Box 7)
    - On road to Lafon Hill near Juba in Latuka country, May 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0356 (Box 7)
    - On road to Lafon Hill in Latuka country near Juba, May 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0357 (Box 7)
    - Lafon Hill; my police escort, May 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0358 (Box 7)
    - Pari Lakoro types at Lafon Hill, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0359 (Box 7)
    - Pari Lakoro types at Lafon Hill Equatoria, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0360 (Box 7)
    - Wrist amulets of Pari at Lafon Hill, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0361 (Box 7)
    - Recording Pari Lakoro mall singers at Lafon Hill; Equatoria, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0362 (Box 7)
    - Pari Lokoro playing a tung at Lafon Hill; Equatoria, Sudan, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0363 (Box 7)
    - Pari Lokoro chief and man playing tung; Lafon Hill; Equatoria, Ludon, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0364 (Box 7)
    - Pari Lokoro female grinding dura; Equatoria Province; Sudan, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0365 (Box 7)
  - Subseries 7: Mahdi family #1 (Saadig, Sarah, Hafia, Sayeeda Abdel Rahman, Feisal). Personal family life at home, views of house in Omdurman, grounds, etc., March-September 1963
    - Roxane before Saadig's gate in Omdurman, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0366 (Box 7)
    - Roxane, Abdullah, cook; gate at Sadig's house; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0367 (Box 7)
    - Roxane, Abdullah, and gatekeeper in Saadig's home; Omdurman, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0368 (Box 7)
    - View overlooking Nile from Upper terrace of Sarrah's home in Omdurman, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0369 (Box 7)
    - Sarrah el Mahdi indoors in her home in Omdurman, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0370 (Box 7)
    - Sarrah el Mahdi holding a child, and another woman holding a child, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0371 (Box 7)
    - Sayeeda Abdel Rahman and Sudig at home; Omdurman, June 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0372 (Box 7)
    - Saadig mother Sayeeda; Rahman and grandson; Adbel el Mahdi, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0373 (Box 7)
    - Sayeeda Abdel Rahman and lunch tray; Omdurman, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0374 (Box 7)
    - Sayeeda Abdel Rahman and Sarrah on phone; Omdurman, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0375 (Box 7)
    - Sayeeda Abdel Rahman and Sarrah on phone; Omdurman, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0376 (Box 7)
    - Sarrah and her niece, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0377 (Box 7)
    - Sarrah el Mahdi, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0378 (Box 7)
    - Sarrah el Mahdi, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0379 (Box 7)
    - Sarrah, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0380 (Box 7)
    - Roxane on terrace of Sarrah's home, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0381 (Box 7)
    - Abdullah, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0382 (Box 7)
    - Abdullah, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0383 (Box 7)
    - Abdullah, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0384 (Box 7)
    - Roxane in Sarrah's garden writing, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0385 (Box 7)
    - Roxane working on terrace of Saadig's home; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0386 (Box 7)
    - View towards Hafin's home from Sarrah el Mahdi's sleeping terrace, March 30, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0387 (Box 7)
    - View of gardens from upper terrace of Sarrah el Mahdi's home in Omdurman, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0388 (Box 7)
    - Hafia's garden; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0389 (Box 7)
    - Hafia el Mahdi's garden; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0390 (Box 7)
    - Feisal el Mahdi, Hafia's garden, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0391 (Box 7)
    - Hafia's daughter, Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0392 (Box 7)
    - Saadig and Hafia at home; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0393 (Box 7)
    - Saadig and Hafia in garden of Hafia's house, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0394 (Box 7)
    - Hafia el Mahdi; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0395 (Box 7)
    - Hafia el Mahdi; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0396 (Box 7)
    - Hafia el Mahdi in Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0397 (Box 7)
    - Hafia in her garden; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0398 (Box 7)
    - Hafia in her garden; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0399 (Box 7)
    - Hafia el Mahdi in her garden in Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0400 (Box 7)
    - Hafia at home in her garden; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0401 (Box 8)
    - Hafia in her garden; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0402 (Box 8)
    - Hafia at home in her garden; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0403 (Box 8)
    - Hafia in her garden; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0404 (Box 8)
    - Hafia walking in her garden; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0405 (Box 8)
    - Hafia el Mahdi with Saadig's Mercedes; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0406 (Box 8)
    - Hafia at home with Saadig's Mercedes, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0407 (Box 8)
    - Hafia el Mahdi at home in Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0408 (Box 8)
    - Hafia on garden terrace of her home; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0409 (Box 8)
    - Hafia on terrace of her home in Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0410 (Box 8)
    - Hafia el Mahdi at home in her garden, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0411 (Box 8)
    - Hafia in her garden; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0412 (Box 8)
    - Hafia el Mahdi; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0413 (Box 8)
    - Hafia and her daughter at her home in Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0414 (Box 8)
    - Hafia el Mahdi and daughter at home; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0415 (Box 8)
    - Hafia and daughter; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0416 (Box 8)
    - Hafia in her garden; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0417 (Box 8)
    - Mahdi Nile garden; Omdurman, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0418 (Box 8)
    - Mahdi boat and Nile garden; Omdurman, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0419 (Box 8)
    - Nile garden of Mahdi family; Omdurman, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0420 (Box 8)
    - Nile garden of Mahdi family, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0421 (Box 8)
    - Taher el Fadil in Nile garden, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0422 (Box 8)
    - Taher el Fadl; Nile garden, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0423 (Box 8)
    - Taher el Fadil; Nile garden, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0424 (Box 8)
    - Taher el Fadil in Nile garden, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0425 (Box 8)
    - Taher el Fadil, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0426 (Box 8)
    - Taher el Fadil, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0427 (Box 8)
    - Gazelle in garden arbor, Saarah's home, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0428 (Box 8)
    - Gazelle in Sarrah's garden; Omdurman, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0429 (Box 8)
    - The gazelle, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0430 (Box 8)
    - The gazelle, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0431 (Box 8)
    - The gazelle in the Mahdi garden, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0432 (Box 8)
    - Saadig el Mahdi's car at home in Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0433 (Box 8)
    - Saadig el Mahdi's chauffeur and car; Omdurman, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0434 (Box 8)
    - Mahdi family adieux to Sayeeda A. Rahman; Omdurman, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0435 (Box 8)
    - Mahdi family adieux to Sayeeda A. Rahman; Omdurman, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0436 (Box 8)
    - Mahdi family goodbye to Sayeeda A. Rahman, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0437 (Box 8)
    - Mahdi family Sala, Saadig, Noon, Saarah, at Sayeeda Rahman's departure for Paris, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0438 (Box 8)
    - Abdullah at airport in Khartoum, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0439 (Box 8)
    - Feisal leaning on his car to talk to Sayeeda Rahman at airport; Khartoum, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0440 (Box 8)
    - Feisal at Khartoum airport, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0441 (Box 8)
    - Sayddea Abdel Rahman's plane at Khartoum airport, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0442 (Box 8)
  - Subseries 8: Mahdi family #2 - House of the Imam and grounds, Mahdi home gardens, views of Omdurman, tomb, Khalifa's house, Sheika ritual (Sheika and Zar rite), Sugg, old and modern Omdurman, portrait and drums with ladies attending, August-September 1963
    - Path to Imam's house; Omdurman, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0443 (Box 8)
    - Garden of Imam's house; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0444 (Box 8)
    - Side view of Imam's house, September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0445 (Box 8)
    - The Mahdi's descendent the Imam uses this house; Omdurman, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0446 (Box 8)
    - Flowers in Imam's garden in Omdurman, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0447 (Box 8)
    - Imam's house in Omdurman, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0448 (Box 8)
    - Imam's house in Omdurman, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0449 (Box 8)
    - Shoes removed by two men before entering Imam's home; Omdurman, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0450 (Box 8)
    - Outside Imam's house in Omdurman, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0451 (Box 8)
    - Imam's home; Omdurman, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0452 (Box 8)
    - Flowers in the foreground, and Mahdi's tomb in the background, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0453 (Box 8)
    - Flowers in the foreground, and Mahdi's tomb in the background, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0454 (Box 8)
    - Mahdi's tomb and trees, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0455 (Box 8)
    - Mahdi's tomb and trees, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0456 (Box 8)
    - Side view of Mahdi's tomb, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0457 (Box 8)
    - Mahdi's tomb; cupola from below; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0458 (Box 8)
    - Inside compound of mahdi's tomb; Omdurman, September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0459 (Box 8)
    - Entrance to Mahdi's tomb; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0460 (Box 8)
    - Compound of Mahdi's tomb; gatekeeper's water; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0461 (Box 8)
    - Square before Mahdi's tomb; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0462 (Box 8)
    - Square before Mahdi's tomb; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0463 (Box 8)
    - Lights of Omdurman; Mulid of Prophet, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Ektachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0464 (Box 8)
    - Square for Ansari public gatherings; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0465 (Box 8)
    - Khalifa's house; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0466 (Box 8)
    - Old gate at Khalifa's house; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0467 (Box 8)
    - Khalifa's house in Omdurman; tomb spire of Mahdi's tomb, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0468 (Box 8)
    - Khalifa's house; Omdurman; inscription at entrance, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0469 (Box 8)
    - Plaque in Khalifa's house; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0470 (Box 8)
    - Khalifa's house; Sadik, Mohammed of Mahdi's family, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0471 (Box 8)
    - Sadik Mohammed Nui's [?] wife and son; Omdurman, March 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0472 (Box 8)
    - Khalifa's house; Abdel Baset and Saadiq [?]; Mohammed, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0473 (Box 8)
    - Copper war drum of Ansari in Khalifa's house; Omdurman; very old, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0474 (Box 8)
    - Copper was drum of Ansari in Khalifa's house; Omdurman, April 1975, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0475 (Box 8)
    - Copper war drum of Ansari in Khalifa's house; Omdurman, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0476 (Box 8)
    - Ansari drum inside Khalifa's house; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0477 (Box 8)
    - Khalifa's house; stairs going nowhere; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0478 (Box 8)
    - Khalifa's house; Omdurman; Original tomb spire, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0479 (Box 8)
    - View of Mahdi's tomb from roof of Khalifa's house, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0480 (Box 8)
    - Roxane and schoolchild in front of Khalifa's house; Omdurman, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0481 (Box 8)
    - Village near Jebel Auliya, May 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0482 (Box 8)